<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
<channel>
<title>Lars Blogger</title>
<link>https://iurix.com/blog/</link>
<description>Lars Blogger</description>
<generator>OpenACS 5.0</generator>
<lastBuildDate>Fri, 22 May 2020 18:42:31 GMT</lastBuildDate>
<image>
<title>Lars Blogger</title>
<url>https://iurix.com/rss-support/images/openacs_logo_rss.gif</url>
<link>https://iurix.com/blog/</link>
<width>126</width>
<height>48</height>
</image>
<item>
<title>{This Week: Italy-China Relations, Reopening China&#39;s Economy, and More}</title>
<link>https://iurix.com/blog/one-entry?entry_id=2844</link>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://iurix.com/blog/one-entry?entry_id=2844</guid>
<description>View in browserMay 22, 2020Playing with fire: Italy, China, and Europe&amp;nbsp;Italy&#39;s decision to endorse China&#39;s Belt and Road Initiative in 2019 has created controversy in Europe. Now, the devastating economic impact of the COVID-19 pandemic risks pushing Italy further into China’s arms, argues Giovanna De Maio.&amp;nbsp;Read moreIraq and the US still need each other&amp;nbsp;Iraq&#39;s new prime minister, Mustafa Kadhimi, will have to make progress on two policy fronts, write Michael O&#39;Hanlon and Sara ...</description>
<pubDate>Fri, 22 May 2020 18:42:31 GMT</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>{Your Postman Monthly Newsletter, May 2020}</title>
<link>https://iurix.com/blog/one-entry?entry_id=2840</link>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://iurix.com/blog/one-entry?entry_id=2840</guid>
<description>To view this email as a web page,&amp;nbsp;click here&amp;nbsp;May 2020 Newsletter&amp;nbsp;Mark your calendar for June 24, 2020, 8:00 a.m. (PDT)In the &#34;Build Better APIs with Postman API Builder&#34; webinar, we’ll be walking through a technical demonstration of how you can use Postman’s new API Builder to build higher-quality APIs, speed up API development, and increase API adoption.Topics include:Organizing your API elements around your API schemaMaking API elements shareable and collaborativeCreating,...</description>
<pubDate>Fri, 22 May 2020 18:25:21 GMT</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>{First contact with the &#39;randonauts&#39;}</title>
<link>https://iurix.com/blog/one-entry?entry_id=2836</link>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://iurix.com/blog/one-entry?entry_id=2836</guid>
<description>Your round-up of the latest, greatest data storiesHello,As Apple and Google&amp;nbsp;release their Covid-19 contact tracing technology, the UK’s own contact tracing app has been&amp;nbsp;dogged by privacy concerns&amp;nbsp;after a pilot on the Isle of Wight. The data collected by the UK’s app could, according to researchers, be used to re-identify users and potentially allow authorities to monitor people’s social interactions. The UK’s National Cyber Security Centre has said it’s ‘aware of mos...</description>
<pubDate>Fri, 22 May 2020 13:19:31 GMT</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>{Get an offer or book a demo!}</title>
<link>https://iurix.com/blog/one-entry?entry_id=2830</link>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://iurix.com/blog/one-entry?entry_id=2830</guid>
<description>THANK YOU FOR BEING PART OF THE&amp;nbsp;BIGGEST BCI MEETING EVER!g.tec medical engineering GmbH&amp;nbsp;Austria.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;About&amp;nbsp;|&amp;nbsp;Products&amp;nbsp;|&amp;nbsp;Webinars&amp;nbsp;|&amp;nbsp;Contact</description>
<pubDate>Fri, 22 May 2020 11:40:31 GMT</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>{The evolution of the most popular repos since 2012}</title>
<link>https://iurix.com/blog/one-entry?entry_id=2826</link>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://iurix.com/blog/one-entry?entry_id=2826</guid>
<description>&amp;nbsp;DEVELOPER TIDBITS&amp;nbsp;&amp;lt;/&amp;gt;&amp;nbsp;🍪 🖥️Hi!Were you a developer in 2012?If the answer is &#39;yes&#39;, then I would like to invite you to a big dose of nostalgia (and if your answer is &#39;no&#39;, then there is no doubt you need to see this).But I&#39;m jumping ahead too much. Let&#39;s start at the beginning: since we love data at CodersRank, we created a dynamic video about contributed repositories by using public data from GitHub. More specifically, we wanted to see how the popularity of differe...</description>
<pubDate>Fri, 22 May 2020 11:39:21 GMT</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>{&#34;This is how I turned my old laptop into a server.&#34; + 6 more
 must-reads!}</title>
<link>https://iurix.com/blog/one-entry?entry_id=2818</link>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://iurix.com/blog/one-entry?entry_id=2818</guid>
<description>Hey hey!We&#39;ve had all sorts of exciting stuff happening at DEV lately, so I wanted to share the two I&#39;m most excited about: 1) Yours truly is a co-host of&amp;nbsp;DEV&#39;s first official podcast, DevDiscuss, and 2) Coil is offering all Grant For The Web Hackathon participants&amp;nbsp;a free, 3-month trial.If you check out our podcast, please consider writing a review. 🙏📚 Top 7 Posts From Last Week 📚1.&amp;nbsp;In defense of the modern web: a look at the current state of the web and areas of improv...</description>
<pubDate>Fri, 22 May 2020 11:38:21 GMT</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>{Reduce Your Breach Risk with a Password Manager}</title>
<link>https://iurix.com/blog/one-entry?entry_id=2822</link>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://iurix.com/blog/one-entry?entry_id=2822</guid>
<description>PCI DSS compliance news updates.&amp;nbsp;View in browserReduce Your Breach Risk with a Password ManagerPublished by Admin • May 21, 2020Guest post by&amp;nbsp;ConsumersAdvocate.org&amp;nbsp;It’s the Little Things that Sting Password proliferation is a common cause for complaint in the business world. One recent study found that the average business user has 191 passwords to keep track of. And that figure primarily reflects the “civilians” ...&amp;nbsp;Read moreThe post&amp;nbsp;Reduce Your Breach Risk wi...</description>
<pubDate>Fri, 22 May 2020 11:38:21 GMT</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>{Modern Web Scraping with Python and Selenium}</title>
<link>https://iurix.com/blog/one-entry?entry_id=2806</link>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://iurix.com/blog/one-entry?entry_id=2806</guid>
<description>&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Modern Web Scraping with Python and SeleniumWeb scraping has been around since the early days of the World Wide Web, but scraping modern sites that heavily rely on new technologies is anything but straightforward.In this article, Toptal Software Developer Neal Barnett demonstrates how you can use Python and Selenium to scrape sites that employ a lot of JavaScript, iframes, and certificates.Continue Reading&amp;nbsp;Save to PocketAbout the AuthorNeal BarnettSoftware DeveloperNeal ...</description>
<pubDate>Thu, 21 May 2020 23:26:51 GMT</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>=?utf-8?Q?The_Internet=E2=80=99s_more_secure_because_of_you?=</title>
<link>https://iurix.com/blog/one-entry?entry_id=2802</link>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://iurix.com/blog/one-entry?entry_id=2802</guid>
<description>This is a friendly message from the Electronic Frontier Foundation.&amp;nbsp;Dear Supporter of Digital Freedom,Certbot is part of a growing number of EFF technology projects designed to protect your online freedom. EFF helped develop Let’s Encrypt, the free SSL certificate authority expanding the availability of encryption and taking the web by storm. We created HTTPS Everywhere to help ensure that users connect to websites securely. We also maintain Privacy Badger, a free browser tool that help...</description>
<pubDate>Thu, 21 May 2020 23:25:41 GMT</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>{=?utf-8?Q?Knomi=C2=AE_Combines_Face_and_Voice_for_the_Most_Secure?=
 =?utf-8?Q?_Mobile_Biometric_Authentication_Solution_Available?=}</title>
<link>https://iurix.com/blog/one-entry?entry_id=2798</link>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://iurix.com/blog/one-entry?entry_id=2798</guid>
<description>View in browser&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Knomi®&amp;nbsp;Combines Face and Voice for the Most Secure Mobile Biometric Authentication Solution Available&amp;nbsp;The best performing device-independent authentication solution just got better. Knomi®−Aware&#39;s field-proven mobile biometric authentication framework−now offers a new voice biometric capability called speaker recognition, which when combined with it&#39;s already high-performing facial recognition, presents an ideal choice for a well-integrated, sec...</description>
<pubDate>Thu, 21 May 2020 23:24:31 GMT</pubDate>
</item>
</channel>
</rss>

